I'm doing a risk analysis
to see what's more expensive:
drilling the well
or getting sued.
What'd you come up with?
We're pretty fucked either way.
You know. that place can be
pretty rough at night.
Behind the bar is
the safest spot.
In front of the bar's
a completely different story.
Oh!
This is Charles Newsom.
He's a geologist who specializes
in offshore drilling.
- [Cami] You think that's gas?
- [Nathan] The likelihood
of a successful strike
is ten percent.
A ten percent chance of rain
is no chance at all.
And you think it's there?
- There's no question it's there.
- Go find it.
[Rebecca]
I said explain it...
- Hey.
- Not sell it
- like a fucking time-share.
- You know. me personally.
I prefer
the relationship to evolve
just a little bit further
before I start fucking
lying for somebody.
We don't have a "relationship."
[Tommy] You're abandoning
a sure thing for a maybe.
It's your company.
Who knows. maybe you're right.
I want success.
Get that for me.
I'm telling you. it won't work.
I gave her my word. Tommy.
Does it kill the company?
Absolutely.
but that company died
when her husband died.
Her husband was the best.
but she ain't her husband.
♪ Upbeat rock music ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪♪
[Tommy] I need all the shit
on the rig before we tow it.
Because it'll cost
five times as much
if we drive the ship down there
onto the barge. that's why.
[Dale] No. no. no. I need
the specs on the bridge itself.
- What? What did you say?
- [Dale] No. no. no! No! I know
it's not a fucking drawbridge.
that's why we're taking it down.
- Well. yeah. hey. but...
- Have to p-put me on hold.
- Hey. Nate? Nate?
- [Nathan] Hmm?
Does DOT approve of us
taking down the bridge?
Yes. but we also need
MARAD. LOTA and LDNR.
- I'm on with LDNR right now.
- [Dale] Well. this little boy.
he's saying that we need
Coast Guard approval
- or some shit.
- You there?
[Nathan]
Once LOTA and LDNR sign off...
- [Dale] Uh-huh.
- Then we go to MARAD.
- then we go to the Coast Guard.
- [Tommy stammers] Hang on.
Dale.
Let the lawyer play lawyer.
- Please.
- All right.
- [Nathan] Yep.
- [Angela] I know.
But I don't understand
why she can't stay
- at a hotel for the week.
- [Tommy] Are you there?
You know what.
it's a little nuts around here.
- Let me call you back.
- [Nathan] Here. get me a guy...
[Tommy]
No. I'm gonna call you back.
What did they say? Mama?
I'm just gonna call you back.
All right.
- Thank you.
- [Dale] ...just yet. Hang on.
You have to stay in the dorm.
baby.
- It's fine.
- [Angela] I'm not fine with it.
I don't care.
[groans] My baby's leaving.
Tommy. our baby's leaving.
- [Nathan] Uh-huh. Okay.
- Honey.
she's not going to war.
She's going to a fucking
cheerleading camp. okay?
- Just calm down. Here.
- [Angela groans]
Drink that coffee.
- [Dale] Uh-huh.
- [Nathan] No. I'll wait.
[Dale]
Well. put fuckin' Gates on.
He has some answers.
Apparently. you don't.
I'm here all goddamn day.
I'll...
Pop. everybody's running around
like chickens with their heads
cut off this morning. so...
if you want breakfast.
you might want
to put your order in right now.
Ah. I don't want breakfast.
[lighter flicks]
What are you doing?
Watching the horses.
[horse snorts softly]
You not gonna ask me
about my day?
Said your days are all the same.
So you're not gonna ask
to go with me?
We tried that.
Once was enough.
Oh.
You're just gonna sit there
and not complain about anything?
I might watch that View later.
You're right.
they're pretty funny.
Hmm.
I don't think
they're trying to be funny.
but they are.
So that's all you're gonna do?
I think I got physical therapy
this afternoon.
[chuckles] Okay.
That explains it.
I knew it'd work.
- That was you?
- Happy birthday.
Merry Christmas. and any other
holiday that warrants a gift.
And I think Cheyenne
covers it all.
That she does.
[Tommy]
Well. just so you know.
she ain't exactly got a...
degree in physical therapy.
so if she asks you to do
any weird backbends
or climb up the drainpipe.
don't do it.
Son. there is very little
Cheyenne can ask me
to do that I wouldn't try.
[chuckles]
Yeah. well...
I guess there's
worse ways to go.
Hey. scoop that shit
out of there.
I got aqua therapy
this afternoon.
[groans] Damn it.
♪ Quiet. atmospheric music ♪
Okay. you happy now?
This ain't no
fucking frat house.
It's about as close
as you can get to one.
I'll see you later.
Yeah.
[door opens]
[door closes]
When's the plane get here. Nate?
- Plane's ready.
- All right. You ready. honey?
- We're gonna drive.
- To Fort Worth?
We need the time to talk.
Our baby is a woman now.
Yeah. yeah. I know. honey.
I-I don't have time
for all that today.
Okay? I'll see y'all
at the FBO. All right?
[Nathan]
All right.
- [Tommy] Bye. baby.
- Bye.
[smooches]
Have fun at your little camp.
- I will.
- Okay. Use good judgement.
- In regards to what?
- Well. if you and your little
blonde. bouncy cheerleader
friends are out on the town
having fun. contemplating
the fifth margarita.
just use good judgement.
- That's all.
- [Ainsley] Okay.
But I typically don't
drink margaritas.
There's too much sugar
in the mix.
I feel better already.
[voice breaking]
Okay. well. bye.
I'll just suffer
this milestone all alone
while you go play with
your little oil tankers.
Okay?
And I don't give a fuck
about sugar in my margarita.
It's gonna be okay.
Don't worry so much. Love you.
Don't walk out on me.
you fucking asshole.
[groans]
[Ainsley] I feel like
I'm forgetting something.
- [Angela] Help us with the bags!
- [Ainsley] Daddy!
[sighs] I swear to God.
you don't leave this house.
you just fucking escape it.
♪ Propulsive music ♪
[engine revs]
♪ gentle music ♪
♪♪
- Oh. fuck!
- Ah. Jesus!
- What the fuck?
- God. you scared the hell...
I scared the hell out...
You scared the hell
- out of me!
- [sighs] My God.
[sighs]
- Good morning.
Well. this felt pretty over
the last time we spoke. so...
I... I made it personal.
I had no business doing that.
Well. it was personal.
It is personal. Excuse me.
I was upset.
[sighs] Yep.
You made that very clear.
Look. what...
I...
What I'm trying to say is...
Fuck. why is this so hard?
I don't want
our time together...
to be over.
[Charlie] You know.
I don't hear an apology.
I'm not offering one.
This is a truce.
Yeah. not looking
for one of those.
I'm sorry.
You were right.
About me.
And it's not...
"one day."
I'm lonely now.
You know.
lonely is what you chose.
I'm... [sighs]
I'm choosing different.
[sighs]
Trying to. anyway. You're not
making it very easy for me.
♪ Atmospheric music ♪
Just making you work for it.
Yeah. you are. [scoffs]
Mm-hmm.
Don't like that very much.
do you?
- No.
- No?
I do not.
But. you know...
What?
But you're smitten.
[both chuckle]
I don't know if "smitten"
is the right word.
Oh. no? Standing on my porch
at 7:30 in the morning.
I think you're smitten
about something.
No. I'm intellectually
astute enough...
- Oh.
- To look past the bad jewelry
- and worse haircut...
- [scoffs] [chuckles]
What are you talking... This is...
this necklace is David Yurman.
- Okay. fine.
- No. it is.
- Well. it shows what you know.
- I'm smitten.
I like you.
♪ Romantic music ♪
I like spending time with you.
And...
I love your taste
in grooming products.
[Charlie chuckles]
That's rare in a man.
You understand I'm gonna be on
a rig for the next six months?
Mm-hmm.
It's...
a shallow rig.
I thought. Just...
- Eh...
- Just right offshore.
It's not that far away. I guess.
Jump on one of those airboats.
- You know?
- Mm-hmm.
Dodge a few alligators.
- Yeah. I'm a lawyer.
- Yeah.
I deal with alligators
- for a living.
- That's right. You're a shark.
[chuckles]
You know.
six months is a long time.
I might require some. um...
you know. some home videos.
Yeah.
Hopefully ones
that violate every
moral boundary
that you've set yourself.
[both chuckling]
- All right? Good.
- [laughs]
I'm. uh. going to process that.
- Mm-hmm.
- And then probably sue you.
[Charlie]
Well. that's fine.
You can sue me. Just...
sue me
after you make the video. yeah?
You know. if you were
from Alabama or something.
we wouldn't be having
this conversation.
- You know that. right?
- I'm always amazed at
the mileage an accent buys you
in the States.
I'd never get away
with this in London.
Well. ten percent is
pretty shitty odds.
It's there. You watch.
Let's say it hits.
Mm-hmm.
Then what?
Well. I'm a treasure hunter.
It hits...
I'm going for the next one.
Uh. before I come visit...
Yeah?
I'd like to discuss the mullet.
[laughs]
- [truck door closes]
- [engine starts]
♪♪♪
[water running]
[Miguel babbling]
How long is your day today?
Uh. should be home
by 7:00. You?
Working a double. So. late.
[sighs]
Okay. I'll. uh. I'll swing by
on the way home. Say hi.
Oh. No.
I don't want you
to watch me bartending.
- Why not?
- 'Cause it's...
I don't know. I don't mind
strangers watching me serve.
Not sure I want you watching.
Don't need
you getting any ideas.
I just want to see you.
- I don't care what you're doing.
- [chuckles]
You're not even kind of my type.
But those stray-dog eyes...
Mm. they get me every time.
[chuckles]
I'm gonna take Miguel next door.
[Miguel cooing]
Hey. if I'm not your type.
what is your type?
Guess "stray dog" is
my type now.
- [scoffs]
- [Miguel babbles]
Yeah. that's a compliment.
Hi.
You ready to go?
Yeah.
Hey. should I get a haircut?
Don't change a thing.
I should get a haircut.
♪ Low. discordant music ♪
♪♪
[yawns]
- Ooh. linen?
- Hey.
Yeah. I'm gonna be outside.
it's gonna be very hot.
Come here.
Outside where?
What's your day like?
Mm. having lunch with the girls.
And maybe I'll go
to the village.
Mm.
Why don't you come with me?
Let me show you the future.
The future?
Do you have a crystal ball?
I think maybe so.
And you said it's gonna be hot?
- Very hot and very humid.
- I think I have
just the right dress for that.
Such a tease.
♪ Propulsive. exciting music ♪
[Cami]
Morning. everyone.
- [Dale] Morning. Cami.
- Morning.
You feeling lucky
this morning. Tommy?
Well. luck never drilled a well.
Cami. Not one.
Well. maybe not. but how many
men did it inspire to drill?
Now. that's the question.
- Is it?
- Well.
that's the question I'm asking.
I mean. how many times
has your gut lied to you?
Well. that's not
your gut talking. That's greed.
Greed's dug a million wells.
Now ask me how many times
greed was right.
Well. I guess in six months
we'll have our answer.
- [mouths]
- All right.
let's get this show on the road.
[airplane engine whirring]
♪♪
♪ Melancholy music ♪
My little dove is flying away.
It's just a week. Mama.
It is foreshadowing my future.
[sniffles] I mean. soon it's
just gonna be holidays and...
[voice breaking]
weekends...
[Ainsley groans]
until you get married
and bring over
your little brood of babies.
Dear God. let them be twin girls
that I can dress. [sniffles]
The whole house is
gonna smell like. uh...
diapers and...
baby powder.
I'm gonna call you every night.
Every morning. And I'm gonna
call you every day
after practice.
Unless I find
a really good day spa.
Then I'm gonna call you
right after that.
[Angela inhales]
- Okay. Go. go ahead.
- Okay.
[sniffles] Mm.
Here I go.
Okay.
- Out into the world.
- Okay.
[Ainsley]
Love you.
[breathing shakily]
If you love something.
set it free.
[Angela sobs]
[breathing heavily]
[sobbing]
[exhales]
God.
[breathes heavily]
[sobbing]
[groans]
Okay.
- [engine starts]
- [breathing heavily]
[automated voice]
Who do you want to call?
Call Neiman Marcus.
[line ringing]
[Jamie] Neiman Marcus
Shopping Concierge.
Jamie.
Angela?
I need you.
Oh. Okay. babe. I'm here.
Okay. [sniffles]
- I'm coming. [chuckles]
- Okay.
- I'll see you soon.
- [Angela] Okay.
♪ Low. tense music ♪
- The elevator's broken.
- Yeah. thank...
- thank you.
- You're welcome.
[grunts]
[groans loudly]
♪♪
[sighs]
Hi.
[quietly]
Uh. three...
Hi.
Oh. Cute.
[squeals quietly]
Hi!
Are you...
- Your roommate.
- [Ainsley] Yes.
Are you on
the cheerleading team?
Do I look like
a fucking cheerleader?
I mean. you would make a very
strong base for a pyramid.
I'm in the sports
medicine program.
Oh. cool.
Looks like they have us
paired up in the fall as well.
I'm excited.
- I'm Paigyn.
- I'm. uh. Ainsley.
Pagan?
Pay-gin.
Like the godless religion?
Um. it's actually Latin.
- It means "country dweller."
- Oh.
Are you from the country?
I am from Minneapolis.
[Ainsley]
Is Paigyn Viking?
You know. 'cause...
the football team.
Uh...
it's still Latin.
- like I said seven seconds ago.
- [gasps softly]
Is that a pet rat?
It's a ferret.
What's a ferret?
From the weasel family.
What's a weasel?
Uh...
basically. a big ferret.
You can say hi.
Hi.
[Paigyn]
Just getting used to your smell.
[Ainsley sighs]
Would you be opposed
to a room freshener?
A toxic airborne petrochemical
that I breathe into my lungs?
So. what are your pronouns?
My pronouns?
Well. I would hope
that's pretty clear.
Yeah. I don't make assumptions.
You could identify
as a sunflower.
You know. I've been told
I look like one.
I use they/them.
You know.
I've always been curious...
why they/them?
'Cause there's just one of you.
and those are plural pronouns.
Just never really understood
the hoopla of pronouns.
My name's Ainsley
and I just can't
really come up with a reason
why you would address me
in third person
in a conversation
that I'm a part of.
So. if you do.
I'm probably not there.
so I wouldn't really know what
pronouns you're using anyways.
so why would it matter?
You smell like the beach.
[Ainsley]
Everyone says that. You know.
I think it's 'cause I use
coconut oil as a moisturizer.
Of all the oils.
it penetrates the deepest.
This one smells
like coconut. too.
I would appreciate
if you didn't use that word.
- Coconut?
- "Penetrate."
It's triggering.
It insinuates the patriarchal
power of the phallus.
- Phallus?
- Penis.
[sighs]
They sure can be triggering.
Dude. I dated a boy one time
and his was like.
it was like a third forearm.
And I used to just spit on it
and stroke it
and pretend to pass out.
'cause there was no way that
tree trunk was going inside me.
Do... do you eat meat?
Are we still talking
about penises?
[Paigyn]
I'm vegan.
I would prefer you don't
eat meat in this room.
I would really appreciate it
if you didn't bring
any animal products
in this room. like those shoes
are probably cowhide.
Oh. no. babe.
These are Jimmy Choo.
I meditate at noon.
Okay.
And I don't like music.
Well. I'm not a musician.
I mean I don't like it
played in the room.
This is my safe space
and I need
my environment crafted
to support my mental health.
I think the...
more attention
you give your mental health.
the better. Pagan.
Pay-gin.
That's what I said.
No.
You said it different.
♪ Uneasy music ♪
Uh... I'm gonna let you.
um. they...
I'm gonna let you...
they... meditate.
And I will see they later.
I'll be back.
[breathes deeply]
[creaking]
[BR] Man. I ain't seen
one of these in ages.
You don't ever see 'em
around here.
- No.
- Up in the Panhandle. maybe.
How deep is this well?
'Bout 1.000 feet.
Hmm. Boy. they just prayed
and drilled
back in the day. huh?
Still producing
five barrels a day.
That two inch?
This is where
our next one's going.
But Coop. this is just sucking
on a little pocket.
You drill any further.
there's no guarantees.
This is a fault line.
Ten. 20.000 years ago.
an earthquake opened up a seam
to a reservoir
about 6.000 feet down.
You got seismic to back that up?
I got six wells to back it up.
We keep drilling on this line.
we keep hitting.
Next one goes here.
Let me tell it to Tommy
and Dale. See what they...
Hey. This is my crew now.
Are you not my crew?
Yes or no?
Yeah. we're your crew.
Okay. then.
We're not running
anything by Dale.
It's your job to drill.
it's my job to choose where.
I choose right here.
♪♪
All right.
Let's start working on a pad.
[grunts]
Just wildcatting now.
- Fucking love it.
- Cool.
[BR]
Yeehaw. Here we go.
If this thing doesn't work.
it's our asses.
Boss.
if this thing doesn't work.
it's a couple million dollars
down a dry hole.
Our asses ain't gonna
begin to cover it.
[engine starts]
♪ propulsive music ♪
[indistinct chatter]
Hi. Gretel.
Picking up where we left off.
Greta. Greta!
Gosh. I'm so sorry.
I just need a quick word.
Well. I got
my dorm assignment today
and I met my roommate. and...
you know. I don't feel
like we're a match.
Let's see.
Uh... Paigyn Meester. Sophomore.
Majoring in sports medicine.
Would seem like it's a good fit.
as you are a cheerleader.
and that is a sport. sort of.
Yeah. it's just more of
a personality thing.
How so?
[Ainsley]
Well. for example.
she wants our room
to be a safe space.
And you oppose
your dorm room being a place
where a student feels safe?
No. no. But...
Well. but
she's deciding what is safe.
which for her is like.
no music. no talking.
only vegan snacks
in the room. like...
[chuckles] Hello. let's just
have a diet that's only carbs.
And she has a ferret.
Can we even have pets
- in the dorm room?
- A ferret?
I didn't know what it was.
either.
But you know those sausage dogs?
A Dachshund?
Yeah. it's like
the hamster version of that.
And it kind of smells
like a hamster. but worse.
Ainsley. one of
the many benefits
of university housing
is the opportunity
to learn how
to both express yourself
while accommodating those
who express themselves
differently.
Yeah. I don't get the sense
that she wants me
to express myself at all.
How so?
Well. for example.
their pronouns...
- Here we go.
- What?
Nothing. I'm just preparing
myself to be offended.
- By all means...
- No. I-I-I don't care
what someone's pronouns are.
I-I just. I mean.
using a-a plural pronoun
for one person
is just kind of incorrect.
- Says who?
- Well. the English language.
Ainsley. I'm not going to argue
the evolving nature of
pronoun usage with you.
They would prefer
you use they/them.
- Why is that an issue for you?
- It's not.
but. so. she's telling...
they're telling me
what to call them
and they're telling me
no music and...
all the things that they need
to feel comfortable.
but they're not asking
what I need to feel comfortable.
Did you inform them
of what you need
to feel comfortable?
They didn't give me a chance to.
Then it sounds like you and your
roommate have a lot to discuss.
Ainsley. I'm not here
to referee issues
between you and your roommate.
That's your job now.
Assert yourself.
Start acting like the adult
your driver's license says
you are.
I'm calling my mom.
Or ignore my advice
and act like you're 11.
[gentle piano music playing]
[Angela sighs]
Jamie...
Someday. it'll happen to you.
You'll pump all your love
into a child
only to watch them
outgrow you and...
Ooh. that's nice.
Cavalli?
Summer collection.
- Mm.
- [phone buzzing]
[sighs]
Baby?
[voice breaking]
Mama?
My roommate...
she's mean and scary and...
and she hates music.
Can you switch?
I asked
the admissions counselor.
She said no.
[sighs]
She said to "act like an adult."
She said what?
She said "act like an adult.
like it says
on my driver's license."
Which it doesn't say anywhere.
[Angela]
Oh. oh. Well. don't unpack.
I'm on my way. Okay. baby?
Okay. Thank you.
[Angela]
Okay. I love you.
[call beeps off]
[sniffles]
Looks like she hasn't
outgrown me just yet.
I'll be back in an hour.
[indistinct chatter]
♪ atmospheric music ♪
Turn it off.
Oh. but I can't see.
I'm meditating.
[Ainsley]
Sorry.
[groans] Just...
invading my safe space.
♪ Upbeat. dramatic music ♪
- [knock at door]
- Come in.
Let me guess:
Ainsley Norris' mother.
Oh. you've got a little
name placard. isn't that cute?
Everything makes
so much sense now.
So. it sounds like we have
a little housing issue.
Oh. we don't have
an issue at all.
- Hmm.
- Ainsley and her roommate
have some problems they need
to work out between themselves.
See. when my daughter
has a problem.
I have a problem.
And when I have a problem.
everyone in the path
of my solution
has a bigger fucking problem.
That sounds like
a threat of some sort.
I've read that
visualization is a tool
that universities are using
to help students
achieve their goals.
Yes. we. um...
We find it very effective
for athletes
and public speakers...
So. let's visualize.
Let's visualize
the level of fucking tornado
that I am prepared to become
over this housing issue.
Just close your eyes
and imagine that.
I don't need to close my eyes.
I can see it clearly.
[Angela]
Mm-hmm.
You know where you are?
M-My office?
Mm-mm.
Not my office.
Nope.
I am...
blocking the path
to your solution?
Boy. [sighs] That visualization
really does work.
What would be your solution
to this particular problem?
- I have three. actually. Okay?
- Oh. Okay.
One. move Ainsley
into another dorm.
- Uh...
- Two.
move her roommate
to another dorm.
Or three... and I think you're
gonna really like this one...
give her a waiver to the
freshman housing requirements
and I will get her
an apartment in town.
- That is by far my favorite.
- Great.
However. she requires
a medical reason.
She has allergies.
- Allergies it is.
- Mm-hmm.
I will draft up a waiver
and add it to her file.
When you have an address
- for the apartment. you can...
- [clicks tongue]
♪♪
[line ringing]
[Angela sighs]
Bowie House.
- Hey. Rick.
- Angela.
- how are you?
- [Angela chuckles]
Any better and I'd still be me.
Hey. is the Sorrel Suite
available?
For you. it is.
I'm gonna need it for the week.
It's yours.
Love it. Hey.
what's the address there?
- Uh. 3700 Camp Bowie.
- Got that?
[stammers]
Thank you. doll. I'll see you
in about 30 minutes. okay?
Hey. do you want me to. uh.
reserve any loungers
by the pool for you?
What a great idea. Yes.
How many girls are on
the cheerleading squad?
- I wouldn't have that inf...
- Eight. ten?
- Uh. something like that.
- Uh-huh.
Save me ten. Rick.
Done.
Thank you.
Thank you. Greta.
I'm not sure what I did.
[sighs] You got out of my way.
That's really sad.
because if TCU really cared
about horned frogs.
I mean. obviously.
they're lizards. but. like.
if they actually cared
about their mascot
or the namesake of their mascot.
they would do something
about the reality
that they're endangered. right?
Because. basically. there's
this influx of fire ants...
- [knocking at door]
- [Angela] Baby?
Did you invite someone?
'Cause I really
don't want
a stranger in my space.
It's my mom.
Aww.
Grab your little suitcase. baby.
I booked you the Sorrel Suite
at the Bowie House.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- How long can I stay there?
- All of camp.
Then we're gonna rent you
an apartment for the fall.
You're leaving?
That's what you wanted.
isn't it?
God forbid you try
to make her a friend.
Speaking of friends.
I reserved the pool.
You ought to invite all your
little cheerleaders to come.
[Ainsley]
Great idea.
[Angela]
That's the only kind I have.
I would invite you. too. but
you said that
you don't like music
and there's gonna be music
and dancing and fun.
and all the things
that you said you don't like.
Quite the missed opportunity.
Bunch of dizzy cheerleaders
playing Marco Polo?
What's the big opportunity?
To make a friend.
Come on. baby.
Bye.
- [door opens]
- [receding footsteps]
- [door closes]
- [sighs]
- [Angela sighs]
- Thank you. Mama.
- [Angela grunts]
- She was so mean.
You ever notice how mean people
smell like leftovers?
Your little eyes
and your little nose
and your little heart
are all connected.
She treated you bad. so you felt
like she smelled bad.
She smelled bad
before she was mean.
Might be the ferret.
How am I gonna get to camp?
Guess I'm just gonna have
to stay the week and drive you.
I wish you could stay with me
all of college.
[chuckles] Well. baby girl.
that just might be the plan.
- Yes.
- [Angela chuckles]
Please.
[whoops]
[engine starts]
[Angela]
Okay.
Bye.
Bye!
♪ Propulsive music ♪
♪♪♪
[chuckles]
[Bella gasps]
[Cami]
Oh!
Oh. my God.
Well. there's humid. and then
there's the Louisiana bayou.
Welcome to Louisiana.
[exhales] What's that smell?
That's money.
There's 73 billion barrels
of oil in the Gulf.
And 440 trillion cubic feet
of natural gas.
Well. thank you
for joining. partner.
I wouldn't miss it
for the world.
- [Bella] Hello.
- Let me just say
what a cute little jet you have.
Uh-huh. [laughs]
$60 million dollar airplane.
Costs $10.000 an hour to fly it.
[Gallino]
Big day. partner.
Big day's about
six months from now.
Mmm.
[engine starts]
♪♪
[echoing knock at door]
[Cheyenne echoing]
T.L.?
Trying to decide
if I'm still asleep.
You dreaming?
Mm. That's the debate.
What happens in
the dream version of this?
If I tell you.
the awake version
might tuck tail and haul ass.
Yep. this is how
the dream version goes.
[chuckles]
I remembered a bathing suit.
Shit. I can't tell
if I'm awake or not.
Let's get to work.
[door creaks open]
[door closes]
This is the strangest fucking
neighborhood I've ever lived in.
♪ Rhythmic country music ♪
♪ You can set my house
on fire. baby ♪
♪ You can turn it
into cinder and smoke ♪
♪ 'Cause this house
is mighty cold ♪
♪ And I feel like ♪
♪ Melting all the snow away ♪
♪♪
♪ You see these boots
I'm wearing ♪
♪ They're tough enough
to go... ♪
What?
Nothing.
♪♪
♪ You can set my house
on fire. baby ♪
♪ You ain't gotta die
to be dead to me ♪
- [cheering]
- ♪♪
♪ You ain't gotta die
to be dead to me ♪
[whooping]
♪ Well. you ain't gotta be
six feet deep ♪
♪ Pushing up daisies
through concrete ♪
- [sighs]
- ♪ You ain't gotta die ♪
♪ To be dead to me ♪
♪♪
♪ He was a-drinkin'
and a-hollerin' ♪
♪ And you know... ♪
- I ordered snacks.
- What kind?
Shrimp cocktail.
chips and guacamole.
- Yes.
- [chuckles]
Tuna poke. whoo!
Ceviche. yum.
[Angela sighs]
Thank you.
[Ainsley sighs]
This is how I imagined
college would be.
I mean.
this is how it should be.
This is how
life should be. baby.
- I agree.
- You know. every day.
you got to find a way
to celebrate life.
I mean. that's the trick.
If you don't...
Well. then you're my roommate.
Ex-roommate.
She's just mad at the world.
- Mm.
- For no reason.
I mean. she has a reason.
What's her reason?
She doesn't like herself.
Instead of fixing
the things she doesn't like.
she blames it on everyone else.
That's so sad.
It's so sad.
Ainsley. we're gonna
play margarita Marco Polo.
[chuckling]
Wait. what is that?
If whoever's it tags you.
you gotta drink a margarita.
- [laughs]
- You in?
- Yes. Want to play?
- No.
[Ainsley giggles]
- [chuckles]
- Look at that little butt.
- [girls whooping]
- [Angela] That's my baby.
Grab life by the balls
and twist.
- Marco!
- Polo!
[cheerleader]
Marco!
[cheerleaders]
Polo!
♪ Propulsive music ♪
All right. Are we ready?
[Nathan]
30 years in this business.
I have never seen a viewing
party for a rig launch.
Yeah. She put her own stamp
on this thing. that's for sure.
[busy chatter]
Thank y'all for coming.
Ah. Ms. Falcone.
This. uh.
this wasn't what we meant
when we said proof of launch.
Well. I'd say this proves it.
though. Wouldn't you?
When I see a rig float by.
We appreciate the swiftness
you put this together.
And I must say. I'm impressed
with the ceremony.
It's unnecessary. but...
impressive nonetheless.
Well. hopefully.
you see our commitment
to honoring our obligations.
It's pretty hard to miss.
- Here we go.
- ¿Que es esto?
- Mint julep.
- Okay.
I like your style.
Well. if you're
gonna take a risk.
you might as well celebrate.
- Cheers. Tommy?
- Cheers to that.
No. I'm good.
[overlapping chatter]
- [Cami] Mm.
- Mm. This is lovely.
[Cami]
Very fresh.
There goes the diet. Dale.
Told you. I ain't on
no fucking diet. all right?
These Cajuns can cook.
I'm eating.
Come sit with me for a minute.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
Oh. perfect timing.
[Tommy]
Yep.
Excuse me. hi. What are those?
Alligator po'boys.
Alligator po'boys?
- Mm-hmm.
- [Dale] Shit.
Mmm.
Oh...
- Damn.
- [Nathan] Dale.
- Yeah?
- [Nathan] It's coming.
[Dale]
Yeah. yeah.
- The rig's about to pass.
- [Dale] Look. man.
I spent two years on one of
them sons of bitches. okay?
I do not need
to watch one float past.
I'm here for moral support
and the food.
all right? You need to try
one of these po'boys.
- What is it?
- [Dale] Alligator.
Delicious.
Very well done.
- Oh!
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- Fuck yeah.
Yeah. okay. It's good.
[Dale muffled]
I know. man.
♪ Gentle music ♪
I understand it now.
What drove him.
There's a rush...
an exhilaration. to the risk.
Las Vegas was built
on that rush.
Don't you feel it?
No. ma'am. I don't.
But you felt it once.
didn't you?
I sure did.
And that rush
cost me everything.
Now. I do anything I can
to avoid it.
And yet you work for
a company built on that risk.
Built by my husband.
who thrived on it.
Who built a fortune
because of it.
He died because of it. Cami.
No. I disagree.
I'd say
it's what allowed him to live.
♪ Melancholy music ♪
President of my company
can't be averse
to the very thing that built it.
What are you saying?
I'm saying you're fired.
♪♪♪
Thanks.
♪♪
♪♪♪
I used to live in Houston.
And when you look up
at the sky there.
there ain't any stars.
All the city lights
drown 'em out.
so Houston ain't really
got a night.
It's just this...
this muddy sky
until the sun rises. [sighs]
What were you doing in Houston?
Same thing I'm doing here.
Minus the physical therapy.
- [chuckles]
What's going on in that
silver-headed brain of yours?
Just thinking.
If I was 30 years younger.
I'd be chasing you around
this pool like a water bug.
[chuckles]
T.L.. if you was
30 years younger.
I just might let you catch me.
- [chuckles]
You want to know what I wonder?
About life.
like. my life in particular.
♪ Gentle music ♪
What's the plan for me?
Life ain't got a plan for you.
You got to have the plan.
Then you wrestle with life
to make it come true.
Hmm.
What do you want?
What everybody wants. I guess.
To be in love. and...
to see the world.
Want to know how much money
I've saved up?
How much?
[inhales]
$162.000.
That is a pretty good chunk.
Want to know
what I'm gonna do with it?
[chuckles] Ain't got a clue.
Me. neither.
Not a clue.
So. I figure I'll just keep
socking it away until I know.
See. you do have a plan.
[giggles]
What was your plan?
My plan didn't work out.
No?
So what's your plan now?
I'm working on it.
Looks like
we have the same plan.
My name ain't really Cheyenne.
Is that a fact? [chuckles]
It's Penny.
Don't tell anybody.
It'll be our secret.
And since we're coming
clean about everything. um...
I'm not really
a physical therapist.
You don't say?
- [T.L. chuckles]
- [laughs] But I like it.
I don't think
I'm any good at it. but...
Don't sell yourself short.
Penny.
This is the best therapy
I've ever had.
- [loud rock music playing]
- [overlapping chatter]
♪ I's made in a field ♪
♪ Full of stick tights
and thistles ♪
♪ Ready from the jump like
a kettle when it whistles ♪
♪ Hot to the touch... ♪
- Hey.
- Yeah?
I'm all caught up.
I'm gonna go check on my son.
You want to watch
my side for me. Yoda?
Cover your patrons. I will.
I don't understand
the Pig Latin.
Oh. come on. that's Yoda-Latin.
- Oh. is it?
- We've been over this.
- Oh. come on. Nerd!
- [Barney] Yeah.
- Beer. Yeah.
- ♪ A panhandle twister ♪
♪ Couldn't break this chain ♪
♪ By the power
of the desert high sun... ♪
- [music continues muffled]
- [line ringing]
Hola. hola.
[speaking Spanish]
All right. Bye.
[Johnny] All you spic bitches
with your nose in the air.
When your job was to serve me.
You're banned from the cafe.
- We're not in the cafe.
- [grunts]
We're behind the cafe.
Well. you're banned
from the property.
You're trespassing.
[scoffs] You're trespassing.
You got some ID on you. wetback?
[panting]
[grunting]
[Johnny groans]
[both grunting]
No! No!
[Johnny yells]
[both grunting]
[coughs]
[Johnny grunting]
♪ My reckless ♪
♪ Is like prayin' for rain ♪
♪ In Texas ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh. oh... ♪
[Cooper]
Hey. man. Ariana here?
Who's asking?
Fiancé. Cooper.
[laughs] Says you. man.
[scoffs]
♪ A thousand stallions ♪
♪ Couldn't settle me straight ♪
♪ A panhandle twister
couldn't break this chain... ♪
Oh. shit.
All right. well.
I guess you're Cooper.
[chuckles]
Oh. yeah. She's out back.
- That door?
- Yeah. that's the one.
- Appreciate it.
- Yep.
- [overlapping chatter]
- ♪ Don't change ♪
♪ Asking me to hang up... ♪
[Ariana grunting. panting]
[Ariana]
No! No!
No!
[crying]
Stop!
[grunting]
[both grunting]
[panting]
[grunting]
Cooper. Cooper.
Cooper!
[grunting]
Stop! You're killing him!
[sobs]
Cooper!
You're goddamn right
I'm killing him. [grunts]
- [Ariana] Cooper!
- [grunting]
- [Cooper panting]
- Don't go to jail
for this piece of shit. Please.
Don't do that to me.
[Cooper and Ariana panting]
[panting]
- [both panting]
- I got you.
- You okay?
- [Ariana panting] Mm-hmm.
Hey. we're starting to get...
What the fuck? Are you okay?
He was waiting for me.
I'm gonna. uh. call Odessa PD.
Hey. stay on your fucking back!
[groaning] I'm hurt.
- You're hurt. pendejo?
- No. hey. hey!
- [Ariana grunts]
- [Barney] Hey. hey. hey.
stop. stop. stop. stop.
- [Cooper] I got her. I got her.
- Stop.
- Come on.
- [whimpers]
- [sobbing]
- It's okay.
It's okay.
[crying]
[Barney]
Okay. Fucking
just... watch him. all right?
Make sure he doesn't
fucking move. No. no. no.
Hey. man. Uh...
the cops are gonna come.
Stay. make sure that
they get back here.
That they can get around.
♪ Tense. dramatic music ♪
♪ gentle music ♪
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today